Hi, this is Telephone Communication Madonna.
Привет, компания Мадонна, консультации по интимным вопросам.
Let's see, your membership number is...
С вами говорит оператор номер...
Oh, you're a junior high school student?
О... вы студент высшей школы?
Hi, this is Telephone Communication Madonna.
Привет, это компания Мадонна.
Don't worry...
Не волнуйтесь...
Riding a blue horse, I put my lips to the glass
Riding a blue horse, I put my lips to the glass
I'm holding back the pain in my heart
I'm holding back the pain in my heart
Everyone's searching in this dazzling city
Everyone's searching in this dazzling city
The place I invite you, to the sky
The place I invite you, to the sky
Sweet music, with just that we motion, to the sky
Sweet music, with just that we motion, to the sky
Please call me tonight, don't forget
Please call me tonight, don't forget
Please call me tonight, once more
Please call me tonight, once more
Hi, it's Natsumi. Oh, Emi. So how's the club going? Well?
Привет, это Нацуми. О, Эми. Я нужна в клубе? Что-то стряслось?
Yeah, not much trouble.
Да, небольшие проблемы.
Why don't you show up from time to time? You are the boss.
Почему ты так редко появляешся? Ты же босс.
Hey, I'm only Natsumi Co-op's owner, as far as the club goes.
Эй, я - только староста Кооператива Нацуми, а клуб так далеко.
I know.
Я знаю.
By the way, Rumi, there's a client that needs you...
Но, Руми, есть клиент, которому нужна наша помощь,
can you write down the number?
может запишешь его номер?
Go ahead.
Диктуй.
Sugiura-san from Mitaka, his issue is...
Сугура-Сан из Митаки, его проблема...
...a problem masturbating?!
...проблема с мастурбацией?!
Hey, Yumi, what's with this?!
Эй, Уми, что с тобой?!
We can't handle this.
Мы помогаем нормальным парам у которых проблемы.
Well, he says his body changes when he masturbates...
Да, но он говорит, что его тело при мастурбации меняется...
Sugiura here.
Это Сугура.
I'm Suuko from Madonna.
Я Суюко из Мадонны.
Oh, h... hi...
О... Привет...
Thank you for calling earlier.
Вы хотели поговорить со мной.
Oh, well... uh...
Да... Хорошо...
Your voice seems dead. This is serious.
Ваш голос такой безжизненный. Это серьёзно.
Yeah, well... when I masturbate I see light and birds and stuff...
Да, хорошо... когда я мастурбирую, то вижу огни и птиц,
and my room gets damaged...
а потом, моя комната оказывается разрушена...
Hey, just calm down, calm down and talk to me!
Успокойтесь, просто говорите со мной!
Well, er... I'd like to meet somewhere... um...
Хорошо... Я хотел бы встретиться где-нибудь... гм...
Welcome!
Добро пожаловать!
Thanks for waiting!
Спасибо, что подождали!
Ashtray on a book...
Пепельница на книге,
that was the sign.
как договаривались.
I'm Sugiura.
Я — Сугура.
I'm Suuko, nice to meet you!
А я Суюко, рада познакомиться!
Welcome! What would you like?
Добро пожаловать! Что закажете?
Iced Earl Grey, please.
Холодный Эрл Грей, пожалуйста.
Sure.
Минуточку.
You must be popular with girls!
Вы, должно быть, нравитесь девушкам!
But about what we were talking about before...
Знаете то, о чём мы говорили раньше,
it's not such a serious problem.
это не такая серьёзная проблема.
I have a friend who's about your age and very familiar with Freud...
У меня есть друг вашего возраста, он увлекается Фрейдом...
according to him the libido is...
Всё это связано с либидо...
Wha?!
Что?! Я...
What happened to your clothes?
Что случилось с вашей одеждой?
Whenever I try... um,  this... happens.
Когда я пытаюсь... всегда... это случается...
Here you are, please enjoy.
Пожалуйста, приятного аппетита.
I guess this is no place for Freud.
Кажется Фрейду тут не место.
It's not fun if it's too easy, anyway.
Похоже, всё не так просто.
I have to spend so much on clothes, too...
Мне прихожится много тратить на одежду...
Why don't you masturbate here?
Почему бы вам не заняться мастурбацией здесь?
No?
Нет?
A lizard might appear. Maybe even a werewolf...
Можешь стать ящером. Или даже оборотнем...
It's fine...
Так хорошо...
face this way...
Необыкновеное лицо...
Hey, are you all right?!
С тобой всё в порядке?!
I...
Я...
Come on!
Бежим!
The Man with a Thousand Legs Frank Belknap Long
Человек с тысячей ног
Sorry!
Простите!
I can see what you mean about the clothes...
Теперь ясно, что с твоей одеждой...
Was that you?
Что это было?
What the hell are you?!
Что за чертовщина?!
Be quiet!
Прекратите!
Sorry.
Простите.
Why me?
Почему я?
What do you want me to do?
Зачем я тебе понадобилась?
I wasn't able to tell anyone... I just wanted to discuss it.
Я не мог никому сказать... Мне надо было поговорить об этом.
So...
И...
Sit down!
Да сядь ты!
I said sit down!
Я сказал, сядь!
So basically when he thinks or sees perverted things...
Выходит, когда он думает об извращениях или видит их...
Oh, I see...
О, ясно...
It feels great, why don't you take one too?
Я чувствую себя гораздо лучше, не хочешь тоже?
This is bad, coming to a place like this!
Эта кровать, многообещающее место!
With my body like this...
Хотеть этого со мной...
Dummy, you think I'm going to sleep with a monster?
Дурачок, думаешь я собираюсь спать с монстром?
That's true, but...
Да... действительно, но...
But...
Но...
I'm very... interested in you.
Ты очень... заитересовал меня.
Looks like we're at the last resort.
Смотри, это последнее средство.
You'll just have to get used to it.
Это то, что тебе нужно.
'Get used to it'?!
'То, что нужно?!
Yes, get used to it!
Да, то что нужно!
Now, now, come on!
Быстрей, быстрей, идём!
Private Video Room A.I.C...er... G.
Private Video Room A.I.C... er... G.
Yo!
Эй!
What's up?
Поговорим?
And then these tentacles were like BOOM!
И потом эти щупальца БАЦ!
It's true! It wasn't a costume either!
Это правда! Это не костюм!
Isn't it interesting?
Разве тебе это не интересно?
An alien, some country's secret project, a engineered person!
Секретный иностранный проект "искусственный человек"!
No, an undiscovered...
Нет, неизведаное...
But he's a pretty good-looking guy...
Ну, он довольно красивый парень...
for one you have a crush on.
И ты влюбилась без памяти.
Hey, listen to what I'm saying!
Эй, ты слышишь, что я говорю!
Don't get weird ideas, sister. He's a monster!
Что за дурацкие идеи, сестричка! Он монстр!
I know, he's a monster.
Да, конечно, монстр.
You're even more of a monster though.
Да ты сама круче любого монстра, хотя...
But... this girl...
Но... эта девушка....
...where have I seen her...
Я её где-то видела...
Oh, first year student, Natsumi!
О, это первокурсница Нацуми!
Natsumi Rumi!
Нацуми Руми!
I've found something interesting for the first time in a while.
Теперь это и правда становится интересным.
I'm taking this photo!
Я возьму это фото!
Oh, Mother, I'm going to Yumi's place. Don't worry.
Мама, я схожу с Юми погуляю. Не волнуйся.
OK, bye Mother.
Ага, пока мама.
That sure is smooth, Natsumi.
Надо же как ловко, Нацуми.
So the top student Natsumi Rumi...
И так лучшая студентка Нацуми Руми
transforms into a woman of the night, eh?
превращается в женщину ночи!?
What do you want with me?
Что тебе нужно от меня?
Nothing... I just want to get to know him.
Ничего... Я только хочу познакомиться с ним.
It's simple, bring him to the Shagai bar by the station tomorrow at 4.
Просто приведи его завтра в бар на Сагаи к четырём часам.
Spend the night thinking about what will happen if you refuse.
И прежде чем отказаться, подумай о последствиях.
What's this?
Что это?
A thank you, for everything until now.
Спасибо за всё.
A thank you?
Спасибо?
Something wrong?
Что-то не так?
No.
Нет.
Nothing.
Ничего.
Hello, it's me.
Привет, это я.
Can you get the gang together?
Ты можешь всех собрать?
Yeah, as soon as possible.
Да, как можно скорее.
There's something....
Знаешь...
I've wanted to ask for a while... but...
Я давно хочу спросить...
What?
Что?
The first time we met at the cafe...
При первой встрече в кафе...
Back then...
Тогда...
why didn't you run away?
Почему ты не убежала?
That was... because starting then...
Наверное... потому что с самого начала...
I was interested in you, Ryou.
Ты заинтересовал меня, Рюу.
Ryou?
Рюу?
Great job!
Ты удержался!
Nohara Group
Nohara Group
Milady, you have a telephone call.
Оджо-сан, вас к телефону.
Hey Maki, this is bad!
Эй, Маки, тут такие дела!
Your sister and the others are doing something with the monster!
Ваша сестра и другие делают что-что с монстром!
They're at...
Они в...
This building has been abandoned like this for two years...
Это здание уже два года, как заброшено
and we use it from time to time.
и мы иногда им пользуемся.
It's good for things like this.
Оно очень подходит для таких дел.
Now then...
А теперь...
Ryou! Ryou!
Рюу! Рюу!
The night is long, let's enjoy ourselves!
Ночь длинная, давай наслаждаться!
Nice and slowly!
Медленно и со вкусом!
Rumi!
Руми!
From what my friends say, you turn into a real monster!
Мои друзья говорят, что ты превращаешься в настоящего монстра!
Now then...
Сейчас...
let's see the monster!
Посмотрим на чудовище!
I know how to defend myself!
Я сумею защититься!
Come and get it!
Давайте, рискните!
Milady, you cannot take something like that!
Оджо-сан, вы не можете это забрать!
Wait! Milady!
Подождите! Оджо-сан!
Now, who's next?
Ну, кто следующий?
You're strong.
Ты сильная.
I like strong girls.
Люблю сильных девушек.
Ryou!
Рюу!
Ryou...
Рюу...
This is cool!
Повесилимся!
Let's do it, you bastard!
Иди сюда, ты ублюдок!
He'll return to normal soon... he'll return... he'll return soon...
Он скоро придёт в себя... станет нормальным... он станет, скоро...
Do something! He's your boyfriend, right?!
Сделай же что-нибудь! Он же твой парень?!
Hey, Rumi!
Эй, Руми!
You pervert! You weakling!
Ты превратился! Слабак!
You...
Ты...
Sugiura Ryou...
Сугура Рюу...
YOU IDIOT!
ТЫ ИДИОТ!
I remember...!
Я помню!
I had lost my memory since I absorbed this life form!
Я потерял память, когда поглотил эту форму жизни!
Wha... What's going on?
Что... Что происходит?
Ryou!
Рюу!
I am...
Я...
I am a collector!
Я - сборщик!
All life forms, from all the worlds...
Разных формы жизни, из всех миров...
Stop!
Стой!
Rumi!
Руми!
R... Ryou!
Р... Рюу!
Why? Why is a part of my collection...
Почему? Почему часть меня сборщик...
WHY?
Почему?
Shut up! SHUT UP!
Хватит! Довольно!
Please...
Прошу...
Leave!
Уходи!
LEAVE!
УХОДИ!
I'm Sugiura from Mitaka.
Я - Сугура из Митаки.
Umm... when I masturbate I see lights and hear birds...
Занимаясь мастурбацией, я вижу огни и слышу птиц,
and when I wake up my room is all damaged...
а очнувшись, вижу разгромленную комнату
Hi, this is Telephone Communication Madonna.
Привет, это служба Мадонна.
I'm Yumi, and you?
Я Юми, а ты?
Oh, really?
Правда?
Hello, this is telecom Madonna.
Привет, служба Мадонна.
Is that good enough?
У меня хорошо вышло?
So what do you want?
Чего вы хотите?
You... what are you wearing right now?
Вы... Что на вас сейчас надето?
What colour is your underwear?
Какого цвета ваше нижнее бельё?
I heard my sister was working here so...
Я слышала, моя сестра устроилась к вам сюда.
Yeah, it's only her second day, but I hear she's doing well.
Да, всего второй день, но уже неплохо справляется.
Everyone's really impressed.
Это весьма впечатляюще.
I'm scared!
Я боюсь!
I'm done!
Закончено!
Yay!
Класс!
Per-ver-t.
Из...
Riding a blue horse, I put my lips to the glass
Riding a blue horse, I put my lips to the glass
I'm holding back the pain in my heart
I'm holding back the pain in my heart
Everyone's searching in this dazzling city
Everyone's searching in this dazzling city
The place I invite you, to the sky
The place I invite you, to the sky
Sweet music, with just that we motion, to the sky
Sweet music, with just that we motion, to the sky
Please call me tonight, don't forget
Please call me tonight, don't forget
Please call me tonight, once more
Please call me tonight, once more
Staring at the changing signal
Staring at the changing signal
The tension of a dream in the way
The tension of a dream in the way
Secluded maybe-woulds, unlucky mayday, tears in motion, in the way
Secluded maybe-woulds, unlucky mayday, tears in motion, in the way
Please call me tonight, please
Please call me tonight, please
Please call me tonight, once more
Please call me tonight, once more